Office of the Boards of Advisors Records UA200
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of the Boards of Advisors Records
1897 -- 2020
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of the Boards of Overseers
Office of the Boards of Advisors
Board of Overseers for Arts and Sciences
Board of Overseers for Athletics
Board of Overseers for the School of Dental Medicine
Board of Overseers for the School of Engineering
Board of Overseers for the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
Board of Visitors for the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
Board of Overseers for the Library
International Board of Overseers
Board of Overseers for the School of Medicine and the Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences
Board of Overseers for the Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
Board of Advocates to the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service
Board of Overseers for the Cummings School of Veterninary Medicine
UA200
20.4 Linear Feet 17 boxes
257 Digital Object(s) Of the 257 digital objects in this collection, 18 represent zip files comprising 52 files and 1.66 MBs of data.
This collection contains the records of the Office of the Boards of Advisors.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Office of the Boards of Advisors, 2008-2019.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into 15 series: Visiting Committees and general office files; Athletics Board of Advisors; Arts and Sciences Board of Advisors; Council of the Boards of Advisors; Dental Board of Advisors; Engineering Board of Advisors; Fletcher School Board of Advisors; International Board of Advisors; Library Board of Overseers; Medical Board of Advisors; Friedman School of Nutrition Board of Advisors; Cummings Veterinary School Board of Advisors; Meeting minutes; Biographical files; Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Meeting Minutes and Materials; and Unprocessed accessions.
Biographical / Historical
The Board of Overseers was originally formed in 1899, in response to a desire for greater alumni input in the governance of the university. Its original functions were to authorize all faculty appointments made by the Trustees, and to notify the Trustees of all changes to personnel. Additionally, the Board was tasked with making abstracts of annual reports from Boards of Visitors, and forwarding these to the Trustees with their own comments. After several Overseers voiced concerns about their input being ignored by the Trustees, the Board voted itself out of existence, in favor of electing ten new alumni to the Board of Trustees which would provide it with formal alumni representation.
In 1986 new Boards of Overseers were formed, as a way of consolidating previous visiting committees that were a part of the university's administrative structure; this newer board did not have a connection to the previous Board of Overseers, though both shared similar goals of enhancing the reputation of the university. While the visiting committees that the Boards replaced had largely held supervisory responsibilities, the Boards of Overseers shifted to a goal of both broadening connections between Tufts and high-achieving professionals, as well as using the advisors' professional experiences to "enhance the quality of life and programs at the university". In order to achieve this, they were composed of thirteen boards, each with 10-12 members, representing the College of the Liberal Arts, the different professional schools, and the university libraries. Overseers on each board reported to both the trustees and the president of the university; additionally, each board had a trustee as its chairman. For the 2011-2012 school year, it was renamed to The Office of the Boards of Advisors.
As of 2019, the Boards of Advisors still works with its original mission, composed of hundreds of professionals who advise Tufts senior administration and trustees, with global impact in mind. Their professional backgrounds vary and include business, academia, and the natural sciences, a diversity that allows them to advance the missions of the eight schools at Tufts, as well as the Department of Athletics and the International Board. Their responsibilities include serving as ambassadors of the university, advising and counseling the administration, and assisting in the university's teaching, research, and service missions.
Custodial History
Overseers changed to Advisors by vote of the Board of Trustees, February 2012.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains biographical files, minutes, and reports created by the various Boards of Advisors and compiled by the Office of the Boards of Advisors. This collection also includes materials created while the Boards were known as the Boards of Overseers and the Visiting Committees.
- Visiting Committees and General Office Files, 1940 -- 2001; UA200.001; 2.4 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains transitional files from the visiting committee system to boards of overseers, including general reports and booklets.
  Arrangement
  This series is grouped into files, reports, and booklets.
  Conditions Governing Access
  20 years from date of creation.
  - Overseer Program Reports, 1988 -- 1989; UA200.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Overseer Program: Visiting Comm Transition- File 1, 1987 -- 1996; UA200.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Transition from Visitor Committee to Boards of Overseers- File 2, 1987; UA200.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Overseer General 2, 1994 -- 1999; UA200.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Visitor Boards- Miscellaneous, 1940 -- 1974; UA200.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Corp. Visiting Commitee Reports, 1970 -- 1980; UA200.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Visiting Committee's Membership, 1978 -- 1995; UA200.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Medical School CVC, 1985 -- 1986; UA200.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Visiting Committee- Nutrition, 1979; UA200.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - School of Medicine Corporation Visiting Committee, 1986; UA200.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Corporation Visiting Committee, Veterinary, 1984 -- 1987; UA200.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Overseer Information- Jane Scanlan, 1998; UA200.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Corporation Visiting Committee, Study Committee Binder, 1986 Copy, UA200.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Corporation Visiting Committee, Study Comitteee, Binder, 1986 Copy 2, UA200.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Report to Trustees on Overseer Program, November 1987, Potential Candidates (1 of 4) [Binder], UA200.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Report to the Trustees on Overseers Program, November 1987, Potential Candidates (2 of 4) [Binder], UA200.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Report to Trustees on Overseer Program, November 1987, Potential Candidates (3 of 4) [Binder], UA200.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Report to Trustees on Overseer Program, November 1987, Potential Candidates (4 of 4) [Binder], UA200.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Key Milestones in the Development of the Overseers Program, 1970 -- 1994; UA200.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Key Milestones in the Development of the Overseers Program with Notes, 1970 -- 1994; UA200.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Status Report July 13, 1990 [Binder], UA200.001.005.00001 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Memorandum to Dr. Jean Mayer, Dr. Thomas Murnane, Mr. Joseph Lambert Discussion of Board of Overseers [Binder], 1989; UA200.001.005.00002 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Reports of the Boards of Overseers August 1, 1990 throuhg January 22, UA200.001.005.00003 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Reports of the Boards of Overseers, February 6, 1991 through December 4, UA200.001.005.00004 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Preview of the Overseers Program, 1993 [2 copies], UA200.001.005.00005 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Overseer General, 1994 -- 1996; UA200.001.005.00006 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Overseers/ Trustees Convocation, November 4 and 5, 1999 [Binder Front Material], UA200.001.005.00007 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Overseers/ Trustees Convocation November 4 and 5, 1999 [Binder, 1 of 6], UA200.001.005.00008 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Overseers/ Trustees Convocation November 4 and 5, 1999 [Binder 2 of 6], UA200.001.005.00009 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Overseers/ Trustees Convocation November 4 and 5, 1999 [Binder 3 of 6], UA200.001.005.00010 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Overseers/ Trustees Convocation November 4 and 5, 1999 [Binder 4 of 6], UA200.001.005.00011 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Overseers/Trustees Convocation November 4 and 5, 1999 [Binder 5 of 5], UA200.001.005.00012 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Overseers Brochure, 2001; UA200.001.005.00013 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
- Athletics Board of Overseers, 1988 -- 2020; UA200.002; 2.4 Linear Feet; 18 Digital Object(s) Of the 18 digital objects in this series, 2 represent zip files comprising 5 files and .15 MBs of data.
  This series consists of materials, similar to the "Working Paper" of the Board of Trustees, from Board meetings, as well as Meeting Minutes.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Athletics Board of Overseers MTG. Thursday, October 7, 2004; UA200.002.001.00001 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athetics Board of Overseers MTG. Tuesday, April 13, 2004; UA200.002.001.00002 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletic Board of Overseers Mtg. Wednesdy, October 8, 2003; UA200.002.001.00003 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletic Board of Overseers MTG. Thursday, April 24, 2003; UA200.002.001.00004 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletic Board of Overseers MTG. Thursday, October 17, 2002; UA200.002.001.00005 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletic Board of Overseers MTG. Thursday, May 2, 2002; UA200.002.001.00006 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletic Board of Overseers Meeting. Monday, October 15, 2001; UA200.002.001.00007 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletic Board of Overseers Meeting. Thursday, May 3, 2001; UA200.002.001.00008 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletic Board of Overseers Meeting. Thursday, October 19, 2000; UA200.002.001.00009 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Board of Overseers MTG. Thursday, April 13, 2000; UA200.002.001.00010 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Overseers Meeting. Friday, November 5, 1999; UA200.002.001.00011 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Overseers Meeting Thursday, August 19, 1999; UA200.002.001.00012 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletic Board Meeting Thursday, April 29, 1999; UA200.002.001.00013 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Board Meeting November 6, 1998; UA200.002.001.00014 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Board of Overseers Mtg. Thursday, August 6, 1998; UA200.002.001.00015 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Overseers Meeting Monday, May 4, 1998; UA200.002.001.00016 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletic Board of Overseers Mtg. Thursday, November 20, 1997; UA200.002.001.00017 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Board of Overseers Thursday, August 21, 1997; UA200.002.001.00018 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics MTG - April 30, 1997; UA200.002.001.00019 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Board of Overseers Friday, October 18, 1996; UA200.002.001.00020 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Meeting - August 22, 1996; UA200.002.001.00021 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Mtg. - April 25, 1996; UA200.002.001.00022 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics - October 27, 1995; UA200.002.001.00023 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Overseers Meeting Thursday, August 23, 1995; UA200.002.001.00024 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics April 27, 1995; UA200.002.001.00025 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletic Board Meeting- Oct. 21, 1994; UA200.002.001.00026 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Ath-8/94, 1994; UA200.002.001.00027 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics 4-12-94, 1994; UA200.002.001.00028 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athl - 10-93, 1993; UA200.002.001.00029 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athl. 10-92, 1992; UA200.002.001.00030 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics - 8-21-92, 1992; UA200.002.001.00031 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics 10-25-91, 1991; UA200.002.001.00032 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics 8/15/91, 1991; UA200.002.001.00033 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics subcommittee mtg. 6-16-91, 1991; UA200.002.001.00034 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Ath - 4-26-91, 1991; UA200.002.001.00035 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Meeting, Oct. 19, 1990; UA200.002.001.00036 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Meeting, April 28, 1990; UA200.002.001.00037 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Mtg., February 16, 1990; UA200.002.001.00038 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Mtg., October 27, 1989; UA200.002.001.00039 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Mtg., April 28, UA200.002.001.00040 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Athletics Mtg., November 18, 1988; UA200.002.001.00041 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-05-10; UA200.002.012.00001; Boards of Overseers Office
    Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, Tuesday, May 10, 2005
  - Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-10-05; UA200.002.012.00002; Boards of Overseers Office
    Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, Tuesday, October 5, 2005
  - Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-05-09; UA200.002.012.00006; Boards of Overseers Office
    Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-10-11; UA200.002.012.00007; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-05-02; UA200.002.012.00008; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-10-04; UA200.002.012.00009; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, 2008-05-01; UA200.002.012.00010; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, 2008-10; UA200.002.012.00011; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-04; UA200.002.012.00012; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-10-01; UA200.002.012.00013; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-05-04; UA200.002.012.00014; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-10-21; UA200.002.012.00015; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting, 2011-10-21; UA200.002.012.00016; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Athletics, 2005 -- 2015; UA200.002.019 (Box 19)
    Meeting agendas, minutes, and materials, Spring 2005-Spring 2015.
  - Athletics meeting minutes, 2016 -- 2018; UA200.002.00001; 4 Digital Object(s); .11 Megabytes
  - Athletics Board of Advisors Minutes, 2018-10-16, UA200.002.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Athletics Board of Advisors Minutes, 2019-04-05; UA200.002.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 31 Kilobytes
  - Report from the Tufts University Athletics Board of Advisors Meeting, 2019 October 08; UA200.000739; 37.79 Megabytes
  - Report from the Tufts University Athletics Board of Advisors Meeting, 2020 April 03; UA200.000747; 25.6 Kilobytes
- Arts and Sciences Board of Overseers, 1988 -- 2020; UA200.003; 2.4 Linear Feet; 20 Digital Object(s) Of the 20 digital objects in this series, 2 represent zip files comprising 7 files and .19 MBs of data.
  - Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers MTG. Thursday, November 4, 2004; UA200.003.001.00042 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers MTG. Thursday, May 6, 2004; UA200.003.001.00043 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Mtg. Wednesday, November 19, 2003; UA200.003.001.00044 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Mtg. Tuesday, May 13, 2003; UA200.003.001.00045 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Mtg. Tuesday, October 8, 2002; UA200.003.001.00046 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Mtg. Thursday, May 16, 2002; UA200.003.001.00047 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Mtg. Thursday, November 1, 2001-CANCELED, UA200.003.001.00048 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board Meeting Thursday, May 17, 2001; UA200.003.001.00049 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board Meeting Thursday, October 12, 2000; UA200.003.001.00050 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board Meeting Thursday, May 18, 2000; UA200.003.001.00051 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board Meeting Friday, November 5, 1999; UA200.003.001.00052 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board Meeting Thursday, May 20, 1999; UA200.003.001.00053 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board Meeting Thursday, November 5, 1998; UA200.003.001.00054 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board Meeting Thursday, May 14, 1998; UA200.003.001.00055 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board Meeting November 24, 1997; UA200.003.001.00056 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - A & S Mtg. - May 2, 1997; UA200.003.001.00057 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Board Meeting Thursday, October 10, 1996; UA200.003.001.00058 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - A&S Mtg.- May 2, 1996; UA200.003.001.00059 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences, 1995; UA200.003.001.00060 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences May 2, 1995; UA200.003.001.00061 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Arts & Sciences Overseer Mtg. March 9, 1995; UA200.003.001.00062 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - A&S Mtg. Nov. 3, 1994; UA200.003.001.00063 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Pre-A&S - Visiting Committee Mtg. Reports (Arts/Humanities/Natural Sciences/Social Sciences/Student Life), 1988 -- 1994; UA200.003.001.00064 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Report from the Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting, 2004-05-06; UA200.003.007.00001; Boards of Overseers Office
    2004 Minutes-Report from the Arts and Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Report from the Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting, 2004-11-04; UA200.003.007.00002; Boards of Overseers Office
    Report from the Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Report from the Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-04-05; UA200.003.007.00003; Boards of Overseers Office
    Report from the Arts and Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting, Tuesday, April 5, 2005
  - Report from the Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-11-03; UA200.003.007.00004; Boards of Overseers Office
    Report from the Arts and Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Report from the Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-04-07; UA200.003.007.00005; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-11-02; UA200.003.007.00006; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-04-10; UA200.003.007.00007; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-11-01; UA200.003.007.00008; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting, 2008-04-03; UA200.003.007.00009; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Financial Aid 101 presentation, 2008-04-02; UA200.003.007.00010; Boards of Overseers Office
    Financial Aid 101 presentation
  - Report from the Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-11-06; UA200.003.007.00011; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    A meeting of the Board of Overseers for the School of Arts and Sciences
  - Report from the Arts & Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-04-02; UA200.003.007.00012
  - Report from the Arts and Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-11-04; UA200.003.007.00013; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Arts and Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting, 2011-10-20; UA200.003.007.00014; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Arts & Sciences, 2005 -- 2015; UA200.003.019 (Box 19)
  - Arts and Sciences meeting minutes, 2014 -- 2018; UA200.003.00001; 6 Digital Object(s); .16 Megabytes
  - Arts and Sciences Board of Advisors Minutes, 2018-09-28, UA200.003.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Arts and Sciences Board of Advisors Minutes, 2019-02-01, UA200.003.00003; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Arts and Sciences Board of Advisors Minutes, 2019-04-23; UA200.003.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 28 Kilobytes
  - Report from the School of Arts and Sciences Board of Advisors Meeting, 2019 September 27; UA200.000738; 34.2 Megabytes
    Civil War
  - Report from the School of Arts and Sciences Board of Advisors Meeting, 2020 April 24; UA200.000746; 31.2 Kilobytes
- Council of the Boards of Overseers, 1995 -- 2015; UA200.004; 2.4 Linear Feet; 5 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of materials, similar to the "Working Paper" of the Board of Trustees, from Board meetings.
  - Council Board of Overseers MTG. Friday, November 5, 2004; UA200.004.001.00065 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Council of the Boards of Overseers Mtg. - Friday, February 6, 2004; UA200.004.001.00066 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Council of the Boards of Overseers Friday, October 26, 2001; UA200.004.001.00067 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Council of the Boards of Overseers Friday, February 9, 2001; UA200.004.001.00068 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Council Board of Overseers Mtg. Friday, November 5, 1999; UA200.004.001.00069 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Council Board of Overseers Mtg. Friday, May 21, 1999; UA200.004.001.00070 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Council Meeting - Feb. 5, 1999; UA200.004.001.00071 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Council Meeting - Friday, February 6, 1998; UA200.004.001.00072 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Council Mtg. - May 16, 1997; UA200.004.001.00073 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Council of the Board of Overseers Friday, February 7, 1997; UA200.004.001.00074 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Council of the Boards of Overseers Friday, November 1, 1996; UA200.004.001.00075 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Council Mtg.- May 17, 1996; UA200.004.001.00076 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Council - November 3, 1995; UA200.004.001.00077 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Council May 19, 1995; UA200.004.001.00078 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Council, Boards of Overseers Friday, February 10, 1995/5:00pm, UA200.004.001.00079 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Report from the Council of the Boards of Overseers Meeting, 2007-02-09; UA200.004.018.00001
    Report from the Council of the Boards of Overseers Meeting-Cabot Intercultural Center, Room 703-Medford/Somerville Campus
  - Report from the Council of the Boards of Overseers Meeting, 2009-02-06; UA200.004.018.00002
  - Report from the Council of the Boards of Overseers Meeting, 2010-02-05; UA200.004.018.00003; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report from the Council of the Boards of Overseers Meeting
  - Report from the Council of the Boards of Overseers Meeting, 2011-02-10; UA200.004.018.00004; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Council of the Boards of Overseers Meeting, 2012-02-09; UA200.004.018.00005; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Council, 2005 -- 2015; UA200.004.019 (Box 19)
- Dental Board of Overseers, 1988 -- 2020; UA200.005; 3.6 Linear Feet; 20 Digital Object(s) Of the 20 digital objects in this series, 2 represent zip files comprising 5 files and .15 MBs of data.
  - Dental Board of Overseers Mtg. Tuesday, November 16, 2004; UA200.005.001.00080 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Board of Overseers Mtg. Friday, April 30, 2004; UA200.005.001.00081 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Board of Overseers Mtg. Tuesday, November 2, 2003; UA200.005.001.00082 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Board of Overseers Meeting Friday, May 2, 2003; UA200.005.001.00083 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Board of Overseers Meeting Thursday, October 21, 2002; UA200.005.001.00084 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Board of Overseers Meeting Friday, May 3, 2002; UA200.005.001.00085 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Board of Overseers Meeting Thursday, October 25, 2001; UA200.005.001.00086 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Board of Overseers Meeting Friday, April 27, 2001; UA200.005.001.00087 (Box UA200 Shared 2)